Hello Hello Friends Welcome to my channel
Winners Portfolio of I am your friend
Ramesh Babu, in my channel I
request only quality companies, on one
hand it will create a huge wealth for you in the long term, if
you come to my channel for the first time then
subscribe to my channel and
also watch my old video once, you will benefit a lot,
today in this video I will
tell you about a company doing general insurance business, I will tell you about the number
one company, I will
tell you about the companies blocking the best group,
you can invest as much money as you want in the stock,
50 thousand, 1 lakh, 10 lakh crore,
invest as much as you want in this company, now
ministers can also do this, invest in this company
for 10-15 years and forget about it, you will become rich, it has happened that
before taking a position in any company, first
look at the balance sheet of that company, its business model and if a company consistently
presents good results then only invest in that company, do not invest
in a bad company even by mistake,
your money will be wasted,
if the balance sheet of any company is good,
products are good, and it consistently presents good results then
invest in that company only, so
first of all  Once look at the financial trend of this company, the
revenue of this company was
108 in 2018 and 11:00 06 in 2019
and in Twenty20 it was 12th, the
revenue of this company is increasing every year, which is
a good thing and look at the profit also, the
profit of this company in 2018 was 60000000, the
profit of this company is improving, which is a good
sign and look at the financial statement, the
total revenue of this company was 4th in 2012, it
increased rapidly to 20, the
revenue of this company is increasing every year,
see, in 2012 the EBITDA increased from 350 crores to
100 crores, this year the
EBITDA of this company is improving, but
seriously look at the net income of this company in 2012 was
516 crores, since then it is
improving every year, so it has increased the profit
of this company  The balance sheet is very
good. There is a
possibility of very good rapid growth in the coming 10-15 years.
Why invest in this company? There is no fear
that by investing in this company, forget about it.
Your life will become better.
Ajay,
look at this company. The name of this company is ICICI
Lombard. It is a company doing general insurance business.
What is the business of this company?
Over 4 crore customers have fixed in
amazing growth. Business centers: Car insurance,
travel insurance, students, life insurance and
other insurance. Two wheeler insurance.
Health insurance business. Health insurance
renewal insurance. It is a
company doing general insurance business. There are high chances of
this company's business growing very fast in the coming years. The number of
people doing insurance in India is very less. The
name of one company is Ad Lamba Do General
Insurance Company, a very big multibagger
house, Pune has the power.
Look at the performance of this company. In one ODI, this company
gave flat returns to the investor and look at the
Friday square return. Friday, it
gave absolutely pinpointed percent return to the investor and look at the one month return.
In one month, it gave 10.5% return to the investor
and a six-inch return.  I
gave subscriber returns to investors and for half a minute
this company did not give returns to investors in 2015 and comment 10
share market was
good since then till now it has given 120%
return to investors in the coming
5 to 10-15 years this company will create a huge will for you in the coming 5 to 10-15 years,
invest in this company for your children and through your children and forget it, no
one can stop you from making money,
media appointed you as minister, good company,
invest and forget it, now in the next video
and subscribe till then it is bye-bye